{
    "title": "500 Question Math Quiz",
    "listOfQuestions": [
        {
            "question": "What is 380 / 19?",
            "correctAnswer": 20,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                27,
                19,
                13
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1554 / 42?",
            "correctAnswer": 37,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                28,
                44,
                39
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1248 / 24?",
            "correctAnswer": 52,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                51,
                54,
                55
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1350 / 27?",
            "correctAnswer": 50,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                56,
                48,
                54
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 28 * 59?",
            "correctAnswer": 1652,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1656,
                1657,
                1645
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 71 - 25?",
            "correctAnswer": 46,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                40,
                49,
                36
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 71 + 37?",
            "correctAnswer": 108,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                105,
                106,
                99
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 82 + 38?",
            "correctAnswer": 120,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                112,
                116,
                119
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 380 / 5?",
            "correctAnswer": 76,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                74,
                77,
                79
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 50 * 50?",
            "correctAnswer": 2500,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2496,
                2490,
                2508
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 22 + 26?",
            "correctAnswer": 48,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                52,
                45,
                47
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 53 * 68?",
            "correctAnswer": 3604,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                3610,
                3599,
                3607
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 7 + 8?",
            "correctAnswer": 15,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                17,
                20,
                12
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 82 + 94?",
            "correctAnswer": 176,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                168,
                185,
                179
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 99 - 66?",
            "correctAnswer": 33,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                31,
                29,
                39
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 6 + 8?",
            "correctAnswer": 14,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                8,
                4,
                5
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 43 + 91?",
            "correctAnswer": 134,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                124,
                137,
                132
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 31 * 4?",
            "correctAnswer": 124,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                130,
                123,
                134
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 4089 / 47?",
            "correctAnswer": 87,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                89,
                77,
                94
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 3304 / 56?",
            "correctAnswer": 59,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                68,
                69,
                54
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1027 / 13?",
            "correctAnswer": 79,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                88,
                78,
                71
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 209 / 19?",
            "correctAnswer": 11,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                17,
                18,
                2
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 99 - 82?",
            "correctAnswer": 17,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                26,
                15,
                23
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 82 * 26?",
            "correctAnswer": 2132,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2139,
                2124,
                2135
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 100 + 22?",
            "correctAnswer": 122,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                112,
                114,
                132
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 4902 / 57?",
            "correctAnswer": 86,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                84,
                85,
                94
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 96 * 6?",
            "correctAnswer": 576,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                577,
                570,
                586
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 55 + 64?",
            "correctAnswer": 119,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                121,
                116,
                125
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1116 / 93?",
            "correctAnswer": 12,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                3,
                14,
                6
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2052 / 27?",
            "correctAnswer": 76,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                72,
                73,
                69
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 51 + 53?",
            "correctAnswer": 104,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                97,
                113,
                95
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 36 - 71?",
            "correctAnswer": -35,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -40,
                -30,
                -45
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 93 + 87?",
            "correctAnswer": 180,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                186,
                181,
                174
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 504 / 36?",
            "correctAnswer": 14,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                8,
                19,
                5
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 60 - 7?",
            "correctAnswer": 53,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                52,
                61,
                60
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 92 - 91?",
            "correctAnswer": 1,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -3,
                3,
                5
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 6 + 54?",
            "correctAnswer": 60,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                64,
                58,
                61
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 36 + 2?",
            "correctAnswer": 38,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                45,
                47,
                39
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 8 * 37?",
            "correctAnswer": 296,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                304,
                291,
                303
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 54 + 53?",
            "correctAnswer": 107,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                112,
                114,
                117
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 38 * 73?",
            "correctAnswer": 2774,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2778,
                2780,
                2765
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 5346 / 81?",
            "correctAnswer": 66,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                65,
                67,
                60
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 8 - 56?",
            "correctAnswer": -48,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -39,
                -38,
                -42
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 10 - 16?",
            "correctAnswer": -6,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -15,
                3,
                -4
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 41 + 19?",
            "correctAnswer": 60,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                65,
                59,
                69
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 88 - 50?",
            "correctAnswer": 38,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                40,
                33,
                35
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 38 * 77?",
            "correctAnswer": 2926,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2922,
                2925,
                2918
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 93 * 33?",
            "correctAnswer": 3069,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                3065,
                3074,
                3077
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 4592 / 56?",
            "correctAnswer": 82,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                89,
                85,
                77
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 40 - 41?",
            "correctAnswer": -1,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                0,
                -7,
                -4
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 34 - 78?",
            "correctAnswer": -44,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -34,
                -50,
                -42
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1400 / 28?",
            "correctAnswer": 50,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                60,
                46,
                55
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 390 / 5?",
            "correctAnswer": 78,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                83,
                77,
                85
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 11 - 57?",
            "correctAnswer": -46,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -56,
                -38,
                -54
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 60 + 62?",
            "correctAnswer": 122,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                128,
                131,
                127
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 100 + 3?",
            "correctAnswer": 103,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                96,
                106,
                108
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 74 * 77?",
            "correctAnswer": 5698,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                5690,
                5691,
                5702
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 72 + 41?",
            "correctAnswer": 113,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                123,
                121,
                107
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 16 + 54?",
            "correctAnswer": 70,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                65,
                78,
                71
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 45 - 96?",
            "correctAnswer": -51,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -48,
                -54,
                -61
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 60 + 14?",
            "correctAnswer": 74,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                80,
                73,
                66
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 76 * 48?",
            "correctAnswer": 3648,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                3641,
                3651,
                3644
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 82 * 48?",
            "correctAnswer": 3936,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                3928,
                3933,
                3927
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 83 - 37?",
            "correctAnswer": 46,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                51,
                52,
                53
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 92 / 4?",
            "correctAnswer": 23,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                19,
                20,
                14
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 56 - 10?",
            "correctAnswer": 46,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                41,
                53,
                39
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 41 * 51?",
            "correctAnswer": 2091,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2082,
                2085,
                2087
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 31 + 94?",
            "correctAnswer": 125,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                115,
                132,
                133
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 59 + 53?",
            "correctAnswer": 112,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                105,
                108,
                110
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 10 + 17?",
            "correctAnswer": 27,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                24,
                33,
                18
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 16 + 74?",
            "correctAnswer": 90,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                96,
                89,
                86
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 4345 / 79?",
            "correctAnswer": 55,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                49,
                59,
                53
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 60 + 72?",
            "correctAnswer": 132,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                137,
                131,
                127
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 85 + 36?",
            "correctAnswer": 121,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                130,
                118,
                111
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 55 + 8?",
            "correctAnswer": 63,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                72,
                66,
                53
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 18 + 32?",
            "correctAnswer": 50,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                58,
                54,
                47
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 37 - 78?",
            "correctAnswer": -41,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -40,
                -45,
                -42
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 88 * 3?",
            "correctAnswer": 264,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                273,
                260,
                270
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 64 - 3?",
            "correctAnswer": 61,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                67,
                59,
                62
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 35 * 96?",
            "correctAnswer": 3360,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                3363,
                3357,
                3351
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 6 * 18?",
            "correctAnswer": 108,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                105,
                114,
                99
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 248 / 4?",
            "correctAnswer": 62,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                60,
                54,
                52
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 28 - 73?",
            "correctAnswer": -45,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -38,
                -46,
                -43
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 23 + 98?",
            "correctAnswer": 121,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                117,
                124,
                125
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 59 - 98?",
            "correctAnswer": -39,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -35,
                -43,
                -41
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 37 - 62?",
            "correctAnswer": -25,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -31,
                -23,
                -17
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 42 * 36?",
            "correctAnswer": 1512,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1517,
                1508,
                1509
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 99 + 60?",
            "correctAnswer": 159,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                153,
                169,
                155
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2716 / 28?",
            "correctAnswer": 97,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                88,
                92,
                93
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 8 - 90?",
            "correctAnswer": -82,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -77,
                -92,
                -73
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2679 / 57?",
            "correctAnswer": 47,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                56,
                51,
                54
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 70 + 4?",
            "correctAnswer": 74,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                72,
                73,
                71
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 5832 / 72?",
            "correctAnswer": 81,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                90,
                91,
                71
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 98 * 32?",
            "correctAnswer": 3136,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                3137,
                3146,
                3139
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 768 / 12?",
            "correctAnswer": 64,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                72,
                56,
                62
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 61 * 6?",
            "correctAnswer": 366,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                356,
                357,
                374
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1197 / 21?",
            "correctAnswer": 57,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                66,
                62,
                47
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 95 * 61?",
            "correctAnswer": 5795,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                5793,
                5804,
                5788
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 324 / 81?",
            "correctAnswer": 4,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                11,
                12,
                7
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 42 + 7?",
            "correctAnswer": 49,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                56,
                51,
                45
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 33 * 90?",
            "correctAnswer": 2970,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2965,
                2974,
                2967
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 49 + 7?",
            "correctAnswer": 56,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                58,
                61,
                62
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 53 - 48?",
            "correctAnswer": 5,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                11,
                -5,
                -3
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 39 + 5?",
            "correctAnswer": 44,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                49,
                50,
                37
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 76 + 14?",
            "correctAnswer": 90,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                80,
                81,
                87
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 94 * 67?",
            "correctAnswer": 6298,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                6288,
                6306,
                6295
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 37 * 87?",
            "correctAnswer": 3219,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                3218,
                3220,
                3223
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 52 - 56?",
            "correctAnswer": -4,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -5,
                -11,
                -13
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 3240 / 54?",
            "correctAnswer": 60,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                65,
                69,
                55
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 46 + 84?",
            "correctAnswer": 130,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                123,
                139,
                135
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 56 - 89?",
            "correctAnswer": -33,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -40,
                -27,
                -25
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 5 - 56?",
            "correctAnswer": -51,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -55,
                -53,
                -44
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 946 / 11?",
            "correctAnswer": 86,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                82,
                93,
                78
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 46 - 15?",
            "correctAnswer": 31,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                32,
                36,
                29
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 33 / 1?",
            "correctAnswer": 33,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                35,
                36,
                30
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 96 * 82?",
            "correctAnswer": 7872,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                7866,
                7868,
                7877
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 98 + 57?",
            "correctAnswer": 155,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                163,
                158,
                151
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 65 / 5?",
            "correctAnswer": 13,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                21,
                18,
                5
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 378 / 63?",
            "correctAnswer": 6,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                0,
                1,
                5
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 84 - 38?",
            "correctAnswer": 46,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                42,
                38,
                47
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 38 * 76?",
            "correctAnswer": 2888,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2891,
                2893,
                2878
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1222 / 47?",
            "correctAnswer": 26,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                24,
                27,
                35
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 48 + 36?",
            "correctAnswer": 84,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                75,
                77,
                78
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 138 / 69?",
            "correctAnswer": 2,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -6,
                3,
                -5
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 74 * 42?",
            "correctAnswer": 3108,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                3107,
                3115,
                3102
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 50 - 74?",
            "correctAnswer": -24,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -16,
                -28,
                -33
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2 * 5?",
            "correctAnswer": 10,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                0,
                2,
                3
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 7200 / 72?",
            "correctAnswer": 100,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                106,
                109,
                94
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 3872 / 88?",
            "correctAnswer": 44,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                48,
                46,
                47
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 140 / 4?",
            "correctAnswer": 35,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                32,
                41,
                44
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 87 - 62?",
            "correctAnswer": 25,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                32,
                18,
                19
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 26 * 62?",
            "correctAnswer": 1612,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1618,
                1620,
                1622
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 70 + 50?",
            "correctAnswer": 120,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                121,
                117,
                111
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 84 - 90?",
            "correctAnswer": -6,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -16,
                3,
                -11
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 29 + 11?",
            "correctAnswer": 40,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                49,
                30,
                31
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2394 / 63?",
            "correctAnswer": 38,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                32,
                43,
                47
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 96 * 24?",
            "correctAnswer": 2304,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2295,
                2307,
                2311
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 4422 / 67?",
            "correctAnswer": 66,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                64,
                72,
                60
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 34 * 52?",
            "correctAnswer": 1768,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1773,
                1758,
                1766
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 40 - 8?",
            "correctAnswer": 32,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                36,
                37,
                23
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 99 - 14?",
            "correctAnswer": 85,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                80,
                92,
                94
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 51 * 34?",
            "correctAnswer": 1734,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1737,
                1738,
                1739
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2465 / 29?",
            "correctAnswer": 85,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                88,
                81,
                90
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 46 + 19?",
            "correctAnswer": 65,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                58,
                67,
                60
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2862 / 53?",
            "correctAnswer": 54,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                59,
                60,
                55
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 69 - 98?",
            "correctAnswer": -29,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -39,
                -22,
                -25
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 53 - 47?",
            "correctAnswer": 6,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1,
                -2,
                -1
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 92 - 46?",
            "correctAnswer": 46,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                43,
                51,
                53
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 54 + 73?",
            "correctAnswer": 127,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                121,
                125,
                118
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 6 * 69?",
            "correctAnswer": 414,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                416,
                420,
                413
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 28 - 57?",
            "correctAnswer": -29,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -32,
                -35,
                -26
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 25 + 7?",
            "correctAnswer": 32,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                26,
                28,
                31
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 31 - 41?",
            "correctAnswer": -10,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -5,
                -3,
                -9
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 78 * 12?",
            "correctAnswer": 936,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                940,
                926,
                927
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 89 + 23?",
            "correctAnswer": 112,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                116,
                108,
                102
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 93 * 52?",
            "correctAnswer": 4836,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                4844,
                4830,
                4839
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1155 / 33?",
            "correctAnswer": 35,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                42,
                36,
                45
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 24 - 44?",
            "correctAnswer": -20,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -27,
                -26,
                -17
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 49 + 13?",
            "correctAnswer": 62,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                66,
                67,
                53
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 35 * 1?",
            "correctAnswer": 35,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                36,
                38,
                31
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 56 - 98?",
            "correctAnswer": -42,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -32,
                -34,
                -40
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 47 + 60?",
            "correctAnswer": 107,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                113,
                114,
                99
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 17 * 35?",
            "correctAnswer": 595,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                585,
                588,
                590
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 27 - 56?",
            "correctAnswer": -29,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -32,
                -39,
                -27
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2937 / 89?",
            "correctAnswer": 33,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                42,
                43,
                29
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 8277 / 89?",
            "correctAnswer": 93,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                100,
                101,
                86
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 91 / 1?",
            "correctAnswer": 91,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                92,
                93,
                84
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 75 - 64?",
            "correctAnswer": 11,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                13,
                14,
                7
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 7 + 66?",
            "correctAnswer": 73,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                64,
                68,
                71
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 80 + 87?",
            "correctAnswer": 167,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                162,
                173,
                159
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 79 + 67?",
            "correctAnswer": 146,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                152,
                155,
                143
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 31 - 93?",
            "correctAnswer": -62,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -72,
                -71,
                -59
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2508 / 38?",
            "correctAnswer": 66,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                73,
                58,
                76
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 81 + 12?",
            "correctAnswer": 93,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                88,
                101,
                102
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 88 - 100?",
            "correctAnswer": -12,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -16,
                -3,
                -2
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 5358 / 57?",
            "correctAnswer": 94,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                88,
                93,
                102
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 96 + 35?",
            "correctAnswer": 131,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                130,
                124,
                135
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 25 - 51?",
            "correctAnswer": -26,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -30,
                -35,
                -18
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 45 + 91?",
            "correctAnswer": 136,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                146,
                134,
                135
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 43 * 97?",
            "correctAnswer": 4171,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                4162,
                4165,
                4166
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 35 + 60?",
            "correctAnswer": 95,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                96,
                105,
                92
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 25 - 20?",
            "correctAnswer": 5,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                4,
                -2,
                7
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 4810 / 74?",
            "correctAnswer": 65,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                56,
                57,
                67
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 79 - 59?",
            "correctAnswer": 20,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                13,
                21,
                30
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 89 * 14?",
            "correctAnswer": 1246,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1240,
                1252,
                1254
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1216 / 38?",
            "correctAnswer": 32,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                25,
                37,
                38
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 21 * 49?",
            "correctAnswer": 1029,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1036,
                1021,
                1030
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 97 - 66?",
            "correctAnswer": 31,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                32,
                27,
                30
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 10 + 10?",
            "correctAnswer": 20,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                17,
                21,
                22
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 18 - 94?",
            "correctAnswer": -76,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -69,
                -85,
                -73
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 3936 / 96?",
            "correctAnswer": 41,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                48,
                32,
                43
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 96 - 40?",
            "correctAnswer": 56,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                65,
                49,
                46
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 3 - 37?",
            "correctAnswer": -34,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -32,
                -43,
                -26
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 6764 / 89?",
            "correctAnswer": 76,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                81,
                67,
                86
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 25 * 66?",
            "correctAnswer": 1650,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1640,
                1643,
                1654
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 97 + 29?",
            "correctAnswer": 126,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                128,
                121,
                120
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 77 * 44?",
            "correctAnswer": 3388,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                3393,
                3394,
                3396
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 62 + 77?",
            "correctAnswer": 139,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                146,
                147,
                132
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 7372 / 97?",
            "correctAnswer": 76,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                80,
                67,
                79
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1260 / 63?",
            "correctAnswer": 20,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                29,
                27,
                21
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 34 + 75?",
            "correctAnswer": 109,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                104,
                106,
                102
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 42 - 62?",
            "correctAnswer": -20,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -30,
                -21,
                -17
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 24 + 2?",
            "correctAnswer": 26,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                25,
                20,
                36
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 47 + 74?",
            "correctAnswer": 121,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                122,
                115,
                116
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 9 * 3?",
            "correctAnswer": 27,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                33,
                26,
                30
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 4784 / 52?",
            "correctAnswer": 92,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                96,
                90,
                83
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2 + 44?",
            "correctAnswer": 46,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                56,
                44,
                47
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 74 - 54?",
            "correctAnswer": 20,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                18,
                11,
                28
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 22 + 87?",
            "correctAnswer": 109,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                114,
                110,
                118
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 15 + 37?",
            "correctAnswer": 52,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                43,
                59,
                47
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 4 * 96?",
            "correctAnswer": 384,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                386,
                389,
                375
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 852 / 12?",
            "correctAnswer": 71,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                81,
                67,
                70
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 80 * 40?",
            "correctAnswer": 3200,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                3208,
                3195,
                3190
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 20 - 67?",
            "correctAnswer": -47,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -48,
                -53,
                -41
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 67 * 6?",
            "correctAnswer": 402,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                409,
                411,
                396
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 7 - 91?",
            "correctAnswer": -84,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -87,
                -92,
                -90
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 35 * 48?",
            "correctAnswer": 1680,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1672,
                1670,
                1686
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 5760 / 64?",
            "correctAnswer": 90,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                81,
                89,
                96
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 420 / 7?",
            "correctAnswer": 60,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                66,
                69,
                53
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 10 * 34?",
            "correctAnswer": 340,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                330,
                331,
                333
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 3 * 86?",
            "correctAnswer": 258,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                265,
                253,
                257
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 95 * 58?",
            "correctAnswer": 5510,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                5512,
                5513,
                5500
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1360 / 20?",
            "correctAnswer": 68,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                61,
                77,
                78
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 62 * 63?",
            "correctAnswer": 3906,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                3905,
                3913,
                3897
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 20 - 10?",
            "correctAnswer": 10,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                9,
                2,
                14
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 41 * 12?",
            "correctAnswer": 492,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                499,
                493,
                486
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1 * 95?",
            "correctAnswer": 95,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                96,
                94,
                103
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 7990 / 85?",
            "correctAnswer": 94,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                90,
                93,
                86
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 23 + 46?",
            "correctAnswer": 69,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                59,
                60,
                61
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 6 - 35?",
            "correctAnswer": -29,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -23,
                -21,
                -28
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 97 - 35?",
            "correctAnswer": 62,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                64,
                66,
                60
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 3792 / 79?",
            "correctAnswer": 48,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                57,
                54,
                55
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 35 * 6?",
            "correctAnswer": 210,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                201,
                214,
                207
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 85 - 18?",
            "correctAnswer": 67,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                64,
                59,
                77
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2322 / 86?",
            "correctAnswer": 27,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                25,
                37,
                31
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 148 / 2?",
            "correctAnswer": 74,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                75,
                83,
                84
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 25 - 59?",
            "correctAnswer": -34,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -39,
                -44,
                -31
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 480 / 32?",
            "correctAnswer": 15,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                16,
                17,
                5
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 85 * 95?",
            "correctAnswer": 8075,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                8080,
                8067,
                8085
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 76 * 84?",
            "correctAnswer": 6384,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                6392,
                6389,
                6382
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 42 * 23?",
            "correctAnswer": 966,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                967,
                957,
                975
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 84 - 57?",
            "correctAnswer": 27,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                26,
                35,
                37
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 13 * 31?",
            "correctAnswer": 403,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                394,
                404,
                410
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 71 * 74?",
            "correctAnswer": 5254,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                5248,
                5252,
                5263
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 85 + 23?",
            "correctAnswer": 108,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                114,
                110,
                118
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 65 + 75?",
            "correctAnswer": 140,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                146,
                148,
                149
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 230 / 5?",
            "correctAnswer": 46,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                42,
                36,
                45
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 16 - 79?",
            "correctAnswer": -63,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -72,
                -59,
                -57
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 87 * 87?",
            "correctAnswer": 7569,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                7576,
                7562,
                7571
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 4 + 35?",
            "correctAnswer": 39,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                37,
                44,
                29
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 97 - 31?",
            "correctAnswer": 66,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                64,
                59,
                63
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 46 * 80?",
            "correctAnswer": 3680,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                3684,
                3686,
                3679
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2592 / 54?",
            "correctAnswer": 48,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                44,
                47,
                39
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 144 / 24?",
            "correctAnswer": 6,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                16,
                2,
                7
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 52 - 87?",
            "correctAnswer": -35,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -30,
                -29,
                -28
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 96 + 31?",
            "correctAnswer": 127,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                129,
                117,
                118
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 76 - 30?",
            "correctAnswer": 46,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                51,
                52,
                37
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 12 + 35?",
            "correctAnswer": 47,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                56,
                48,
                45
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 91 * 58?",
            "correctAnswer": 5278,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                5281,
                5286,
                5271
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 52 * 94?",
            "correctAnswer": 4888,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                4880,
                4893,
                4894
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 91 + 71?",
            "correctAnswer": 162,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                168,
                153,
                155
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 294 / 14?",
            "correctAnswer": 21,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                27,
                23,
                31
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 59 * 21?",
            "correctAnswer": 1239,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1235,
                1238,
                1230
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 3358 / 46?",
            "correctAnswer": 73,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                81,
                82,
                77
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 99 - 50?",
            "correctAnswer": 49,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                58,
                44,
                55
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 740 / 74?",
            "correctAnswer": 10,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1,
                18,
                11
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 47 * 69?",
            "correctAnswer": 3243,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                3234,
                3251,
                3253
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 9 * 92?",
            "correctAnswer": 828,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                818,
                835,
                831
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 47 * 30?",
            "correctAnswer": 1410,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1408,
                1416,
                1413
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 30 + 21?",
            "correctAnswer": 51,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                57,
                43,
                55
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 42 * 56?",
            "correctAnswer": 2352,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2345,
                2356,
                2349
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1305 / 87?",
            "correctAnswer": 15,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                13,
                6,
                7
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 364 / 14?",
            "correctAnswer": 26,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                19,
                36,
                31
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 968 / 44?",
            "correctAnswer": 22,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                13,
                30,
                23
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 21 + 61?",
            "correctAnswer": 82,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                81,
                89,
                80
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 3760 / 94?",
            "correctAnswer": 40,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                48,
                50,
                43
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 57 + 58?",
            "correctAnswer": 115,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                122,
                124,
                119
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 243 / 9?",
            "correctAnswer": 27,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                25,
                29,
                22
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1000 / 10?",
            "correctAnswer": 100,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                97,
                94,
                95
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 3034 / 74?",
            "correctAnswer": 41,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                43,
                44,
                38
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 30 * 49?",
            "correctAnswer": 1470,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1480,
                1471,
                1463
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 23 * 88?",
            "correctAnswer": 2024,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2017,
                2029,
                2030
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 97 - 41?",
            "correctAnswer": 56,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                59,
                60,
                54
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 216 / 27?",
            "correctAnswer": 8,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                0,
                11,
                -1
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 28 + 46?",
            "correctAnswer": 74,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                64,
                77,
                78
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1406 / 38?",
            "correctAnswer": 37,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                33,
                35,
                28
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 61 - 86?",
            "correctAnswer": -25,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -24,
                -23,
                -20
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 918 / 18?",
            "correctAnswer": 51,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                57,
                50,
                45
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 6 * 67?",
            "correctAnswer": 402,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                408,
                395,
                412
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 46 - 75?",
            "correctAnswer": -29,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -21,
                -36,
                -27
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 71 + 61?",
            "correctAnswer": 132,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                136,
                130,
                125
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 6 - 67?",
            "correctAnswer": -61,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -69,
                -58,
                -66
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 80 + 28?",
            "correctAnswer": 108,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                109,
                110,
                111
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1060 / 53?",
            "correctAnswer": 20,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                18,
                11,
                15
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 62 - 68?",
            "correctAnswer": -6,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                0,
                1,
                -13
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 290 / 10?",
            "correctAnswer": 29,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                33,
                27,
                23
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 893 / 47?",
            "correctAnswer": 19,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                11,
                22,
                23
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 5952 / 96?",
            "correctAnswer": 62,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                64,
                65,
                54
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 72 + 66?",
            "correctAnswer": 138,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                128,
                137,
                130
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 32 - 3?",
            "correctAnswer": 29,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                32,
                27,
                21
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1980 / 60?",
            "correctAnswer": 33,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                32,
                26,
                43
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 30 + 42?",
            "correctAnswer": 72,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                82,
                76,
                77
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 93 - 86?",
            "correctAnswer": 7,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                9,
                5,
                14
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 4756 / 58?",
            "correctAnswer": 82,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                89,
                78,
                86
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2412 / 36?",
            "correctAnswer": 67,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                64,
                57,
                60
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 57 - 73?",
            "correctAnswer": -16,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -15,
                -21,
                -13
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 77 + 61?",
            "correctAnswer": 138,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                146,
                131,
                133
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 80 + 16?",
            "correctAnswer": 96,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                89,
                98,
                97
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 54 + 47?",
            "correctAnswer": 101,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                96,
                98,
                108
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2730 / 35?",
            "correctAnswer": 78,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                81,
                73,
                72
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 77 * 92?",
            "correctAnswer": 7084,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                7081,
                7076,
                7094
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 5 - 4?",
            "correctAnswer": 1,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                8,
                -7,
                -6
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 64 * 2?",
            "correctAnswer": 128,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                136,
                121,
                132
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 855 / 95?",
            "correctAnswer": 9,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                17,
                11,
                13
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 846 / 47?",
            "correctAnswer": 18,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                16,
                25,
                15
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 92 - 70?",
            "correctAnswer": 22,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                17,
                18,
                14
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 484 / 22?",
            "correctAnswer": 22,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                32,
                18,
                21
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1771 / 77?",
            "correctAnswer": 23,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                33,
                19,
                31
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 64 + 55?",
            "correctAnswer": 119,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                115,
                109,
                126
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 54 - 24?",
            "correctAnswer": 30,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                26,
                20,
                21
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 462 / 21?",
            "correctAnswer": 22,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                16,
                27,
                12
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 80 * 9?",
            "correctAnswer": 720,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                727,
                710,
                719
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 39 + 29?",
            "correctAnswer": 68,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                72,
                66,
                70
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 38 + 84?",
            "correctAnswer": 122,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                115,
                131,
                127
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 3534 / 62?",
            "correctAnswer": 57,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                64,
                50,
                63
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 18 - 16?",
            "correctAnswer": 2,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -6,
                10,
                7
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 76 - 23?",
            "correctAnswer": 53,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                43,
                51,
                54
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 64 - 50?",
            "correctAnswer": 14,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                24,
                18,
                10
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 69 - 73?",
            "correctAnswer": -4,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -8,
                -7,
                2
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 96 * 98?",
            "correctAnswer": 9408,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                9416,
                9405,
                9407
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 4200 / 60?",
            "correctAnswer": 70,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                80,
                75,
                61
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 8 - 72?",
            "correctAnswer": -64,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -56,
                -61,
                -65
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 34 + 63?",
            "correctAnswer": 97,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                105,
                93,
                87
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 67 + 21?",
            "correctAnswer": 88,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                89,
                85,
                79
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 89 + 27?",
            "correctAnswer": 116,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                115,
                125,
                119
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 8170 / 95?",
            "correctAnswer": 86,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                82,
                83,
                95
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 15 * 22?",
            "correctAnswer": 330,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                321,
                331,
                335
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 90 * 60?",
            "correctAnswer": 5400,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                5410,
                5396,
                5407
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 64 * 88?",
            "correctAnswer": 5632,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                5641,
                5629,
                5622
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 40 * 32?",
            "correctAnswer": 1280,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1281,
                1282,
                1275
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 69 - 27?",
            "correctAnswer": 42,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                48,
                35,
                43
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 5328 / 72?",
            "correctAnswer": 74,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                77,
                78,
                71
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 576 / 6?",
            "correctAnswer": 96,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                97,
                99,
                101
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 54 - 32?",
            "correctAnswer": 22,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                17,
                27,
                15
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 70 + 83?",
            "correctAnswer": 153,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                152,
                155,
                148
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 56 * 52?",
            "correctAnswer": 2912,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2914,
                2922,
                2918
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 28 - 43?",
            "correctAnswer": -15,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -8,
                -10,
                -9
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 30 * 70?",
            "correctAnswer": 2100,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2105,
                2091,
                2110
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1734 / 34?",
            "correctAnswer": 51,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                56,
                58,
                50
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 24 + 21?",
            "correctAnswer": 45,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                35,
                43,
                47
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 3900 / 50?",
            "correctAnswer": 78,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                68,
                69,
                71
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 3783 / 39?",
            "correctAnswer": 97,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                91,
                93,
                94
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 63 - 99?",
            "correctAnswer": -36,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -40,
                -35,
                -33
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 984 / 41?",
            "correctAnswer": 24,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                21,
                22,
                31
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 4984 / 89?",
            "correctAnswer": 56,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                60,
                47,
                63
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 5 + 67?",
            "correctAnswer": 72,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                63,
                78,
                71
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 79 - 68?",
            "correctAnswer": 11,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                19,
                3,
                15
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 53 * 60?",
            "correctAnswer": 3180,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                3177,
                3190,
                3175
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2184 / 56?",
            "correctAnswer": 39,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                40,
                34,
                47
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 68 + 49?",
            "correctAnswer": 117,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                114,
                108,
                119
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 6956 / 74?",
            "correctAnswer": 94,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                96,
                98,
                84
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 90 * 31?",
            "correctAnswer": 2790,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2795,
                2797,
                2783
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 7 - 83?",
            "correctAnswer": -76,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -72,
                -78,
                -66
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 50 - 46?",
            "correctAnswer": 4,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                0,
                10,
                14
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 96 + 71?",
            "correctAnswer": 167,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                164,
                157,
                175
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 7533 / 93?",
            "correctAnswer": 81,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                88,
                77,
                87
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 25 - 38?",
            "correctAnswer": -13,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -21,
                -20,
                -5
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 47 * 27?",
            "correctAnswer": 1269,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1266,
                1267,
                1261
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 570 / 95?",
            "correctAnswer": 6,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                10,
                2,
                15
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 100 - 78?",
            "correctAnswer": 22,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                28,
                30,
                31
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 9 * 68?",
            "correctAnswer": 612,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                608,
                606,
                607
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 89 - 25?",
            "correctAnswer": 64,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                62,
                68,
                70
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2961 / 63?",
            "correctAnswer": 47,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                42,
                50,
                46
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 17 - 100?",
            "correctAnswer": -83,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -79,
                -92,
                -75
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 80 + 28?",
            "correctAnswer": 108,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                114,
                107,
                109
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 79 - 38?",
            "correctAnswer": 41,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                42,
                51,
                47
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1782 / 33?",
            "correctAnswer": 54,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                57,
                58,
                60
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 9 - 33?",
            "correctAnswer": -24,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -31,
                -22,
                -33
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 3417 / 51?",
            "correctAnswer": 67,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                65,
                57,
                59
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 84 + 45?",
            "correctAnswer": 129,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                119,
                126,
                127
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 17 - 19?",
            "correctAnswer": -2,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -11,
                -4,
                5
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 17 + 70?",
            "correctAnswer": 87,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                88,
                80,
                78
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 9 * 77?",
            "correctAnswer": 693,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                690,
                700,
                686
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 46 + 42?",
            "correctAnswer": 88,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                80,
                85,
                95
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 83 * 97?",
            "correctAnswer": 8051,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                8050,
                8045,
                8047
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 8100 / 90?",
            "correctAnswer": 90,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                88,
                98,
                96
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 45 - 83?",
            "correctAnswer": -38,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -48,
                -30,
                -43
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 80 - 88?",
            "correctAnswer": -8,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -14,
                -12,
                -17
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 53 - 89?",
            "correctAnswer": -36,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -43,
                -30,
                -27
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 27 + 71?",
            "correctAnswer": 98,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                104,
                105,
                107
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 41 * 2?",
            "correctAnswer": 82,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                89,
                77,
                78
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 84 + 85?",
            "correctAnswer": 169,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                177,
                162,
                175
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 13 - 11?",
            "correctAnswer": 2,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -5,
                5,
                -2
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 300 / 100?",
            "correctAnswer": 3,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                8,
                5,
                7
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 14 * 13?",
            "correctAnswer": 182,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                184,
                177,
                187
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 18 + 81?",
            "correctAnswer": 99,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                93,
                94,
                103
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 32 + 82?",
            "correctAnswer": 114,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                120,
                124,
                104
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 98 / 1?",
            "correctAnswer": 98,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                96,
                97,
                91
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 96 * 14?",
            "correctAnswer": 1344,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1338,
                1347,
                1335
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 43 * 67?",
            "correctAnswer": 2881,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2875,
                2883,
                2878
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 5500 / 100?",
            "correctAnswer": 55,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                56,
                50,
                59
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 68 + 86?",
            "correctAnswer": 154,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                160,
                161,
                158
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 59 * 87?",
            "correctAnswer": 5133,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                5130,
                5132,
                5135
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 77 * 26?",
            "correctAnswer": 2002,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2000,
                1996,
                1998
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 99 - 82?",
            "correctAnswer": 17,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                25,
                13,
                23
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 66 + 20?",
            "correctAnswer": 86,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                83,
                85,
                79
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2312 / 68?",
            "correctAnswer": 34,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                42,
                43,
                37
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 36 - 48?",
            "correctAnswer": -12,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -11,
                -19,
                -17
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 88 + 36?",
            "correctAnswer": 124,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                128,
                129,
                133
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 70 * 61?",
            "correctAnswer": 4270,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                4265,
                4275,
                4279
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 27 - 68?",
            "correctAnswer": -41,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -38,
                -44,
                -51
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 59 + 30?",
            "correctAnswer": 89,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                96,
                79,
                95
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1 - 57?",
            "correctAnswer": -56,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -64,
                -46,
                -60
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 91 + 65?",
            "correctAnswer": 156,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                163,
                166,
                159
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 53 / 1?",
            "correctAnswer": 53,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                58,
                51,
                46
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 34 + 49?",
            "correctAnswer": 83,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                88,
                79,
                87
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 34 - 44?",
            "correctAnswer": -10,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -8,
                -2,
                -17
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 68 - 28?",
            "correctAnswer": 40,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                48,
                49,
                42
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 69 + 55?",
            "correctAnswer": 124,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                115,
                116,
                117
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 10 + 31?",
            "correctAnswer": 41,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                49,
                36,
                39
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 8 - 4?",
            "correctAnswer": 4,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                9,
                5,
                6
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 18 / 1?",
            "correctAnswer": 18,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                11,
                19,
                14
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 47 + 23?",
            "correctAnswer": 70,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                74,
                77,
                71
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 64 + 77?",
            "correctAnswer": 141,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                140,
                133,
                134
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 756 / 27?",
            "correctAnswer": 28,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                35,
                26,
                27
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 45 + 29?",
            "correctAnswer": 74,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                65,
                69,
                79
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 26 * 29?",
            "correctAnswer": 754,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                745,
                762,
                749
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 98 + 37?",
            "correctAnswer": 135,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                129,
                132,
                125
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 14 - 40?",
            "correctAnswer": -26,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -17,
                -27,
                -33
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 2812 / 74?",
            "correctAnswer": 38,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                35,
                42,
                43
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 14 + 25?",
            "correctAnswer": 39,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                43,
                37,
                38
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 252 / 63?",
            "correctAnswer": 4,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2,
                3,
                6
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 40 + 81?",
            "correctAnswer": 121,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                123,
                131,
                127
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 42 + 72?",
            "correctAnswer": 114,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                104,
                123,
                124
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 85 + 3?",
            "correctAnswer": 88,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                82,
                93,
                86
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 66 / 22?",
            "correctAnswer": 3,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -7,
                2,
                1
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 85 + 4?",
            "correctAnswer": 89,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                88,
                98,
                93
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 17 + 80?",
            "correctAnswer": 97,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                89,
                106,
                100
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 91 * 15?",
            "correctAnswer": 1365,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1370,
                1372,
                1364
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 17 + 47?",
            "correctAnswer": 64,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                67,
                59,
                66
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 85 + 100?",
            "correctAnswer": 185,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                194,
                189,
                183
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 50 - 29?",
            "correctAnswer": 21,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                16,
                27,
                13
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 23 * 78?",
            "correctAnswer": 1794,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1785,
                1796,
                1799
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 54 + 4?",
            "correctAnswer": 58,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                49,
                50,
                54
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 30 - 35?",
            "correctAnswer": -5,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -4,
                -1,
                -10
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 29 * 67?",
            "correctAnswer": 1943,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1952,
                1946,
                1936
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 49 * 88?",
            "correctAnswer": 4312,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                4313,
                4305,
                4303
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 34 - 61?",
            "correctAnswer": -27,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -31,
                -18,
                -25
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 98 * 45?",
            "correctAnswer": 4410,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                4400,
                4417,
                4411
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 57 * 40?",
            "correctAnswer": 2280,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2275,
                2285,
                2287
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 87 * 70?",
            "correctAnswer": 6090,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                6082,
                6091,
                6100
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 4 + 29?",
            "correctAnswer": 33,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                32,
                27,
                29
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 19 * 61?",
            "correctAnswer": 1159,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                1160,
                1158,
                1150
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 67 - 17?",
            "correctAnswer": 50,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                57,
                51,
                54
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 5670 / 90?",
            "correctAnswer": 63,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                64,
                67,
                59
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 70 + 10?",
            "correctAnswer": 80,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                72,
                81,
                87
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 46 + 25?",
            "correctAnswer": 71,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                72,
                68,
                69
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 48 + 21?",
            "correctAnswer": 69,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                59,
                60,
                70
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 13 + 94?",
            "correctAnswer": 107,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                104,
                99,
                101
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 52 - 72?",
            "correctAnswer": -20,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -15,
                -28,
                -19
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 50 * 98?",
            "correctAnswer": 4900,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                4890,
                4906,
                4910
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 88 - 51?",
            "correctAnswer": 37,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                33,
                44,
                46
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 23 - 67?",
            "correctAnswer": -44,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -40,
                -53,
                -45
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 75 * 28?",
            "correctAnswer": 2100,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2098,
                2092,
                2094
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 44 / 11?",
            "correctAnswer": 4,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                10,
                -4,
                -1
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 620 / 20?",
            "correctAnswer": 31,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                25,
                30,
                22
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 85 * 3?",
            "correctAnswer": 255,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                245,
                262,
                263
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 18 * 6?",
            "correctAnswer": 108,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                104,
                116,
                109
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 9 + 41?",
            "correctAnswer": 50,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                48,
                59,
                45
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 46 + 68?",
            "correctAnswer": 114,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                122,
                123,
                106
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 11 * 15?",
            "correctAnswer": 165,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                162,
                164,
                167
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 95 + 8?",
            "correctAnswer": 103,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                113,
                100,
                105
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 86 - 65?",
            "correctAnswer": 21,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                28,
                20,
                30
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1836 / 34?",
            "correctAnswer": 54,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                64,
                55,
                47
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 63 - 66?",
            "correctAnswer": -3,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -8,
                -7,
                -2
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 100 * 92?",
            "correctAnswer": 9200,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                9210,
                9204,
                9205
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 98 - 68?",
            "correctAnswer": 30,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                40,
                25,
                39
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 45 + 96?",
            "correctAnswer": 141,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                132,
                140,
                134
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 17 + 43?",
            "correctAnswer": 60,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                57,
                68,
                69
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 18 * 13?",
            "correctAnswer": 234,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                228,
                229,
                239
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 59 + 62?",
            "correctAnswer": 121,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                125,
                126,
                127
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 14 / 14?",
            "correctAnswer": 1,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                2,
                -6,
                -5
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 15 - 74?",
            "correctAnswer": -59,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -67,
                -50,
                -57
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 16 - 27?",
            "correctAnswer": -11,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -6,
                -21,
                -1
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 92 - 98?",
            "correctAnswer": -6,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -7,
                -3,
                -9
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 4620 / 55?",
            "correctAnswer": 84,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                88,
                93,
                78
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 93 * 97?",
            "correctAnswer": 9021,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                9017,
                9015,
                9031
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 3200 / 64?",
            "correctAnswer": 50,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                40,
                52,
                46
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 78 * 60?",
            "correctAnswer": 4680,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                4690,
                4684,
                4679
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 94 + 70?",
            "correctAnswer": 164,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                160,
                171,
                165
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 90 + 18?",
            "correctAnswer": 108,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                105,
                107,
                113
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 63 - 34?",
            "correctAnswer": 29,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                32,
                38,
                39
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 16 - 16?",
            "correctAnswer": 0,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -6,
                -1,
                7
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 5369 / 59?",
            "correctAnswer": 91,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                88,
                81,
                95
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 77 + 98?",
            "correctAnswer": 175,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                184,
                178,
                172
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 3420 / 76?",
            "correctAnswer": 45,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                48,
                49,
                40
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 83 * 60?",
            "correctAnswer": 4980,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                4979,
                4972,
                4975
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 56 - 77?",
            "correctAnswer": -21,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                -24,
                -14,
                -12
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 1476 / 18?",
            "correctAnswer": 82,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                89,
                75,
                92
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "What is 132 / 33?",
            "correctAnswer": 4,
            "wrongAnswers": [
                8,
                3,
                12
            ],
            "timeout": 15
        }
    ],
    "time given": 15
}
